<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ap_terms_of_use">
        <![CDATA[
            <p><span><strong><u>What are the rules for using BBC Adaptive Podcasting Player?</u>
            </strong></span></p><p>Adaptive Podcasting Player is a new experimental media player
            that can play responsive and interactive podcasts created by Adaptive Podcasting Editor,
            a BBC R&amp;D production tool. To play an interactive podcast that a creator has made
            with Adaptive Podcasting you need to install Adaptive Podcasting Player. If you were not
            offered to download Adaptive Podcasting Player by the BBC, please keep in mind that the
            BBC did not create and is not responsible for the interactive podcasts that are
            available to play on Adaptive Podcasting Player. The creator that makes available an
            interactive podcast for you to view through Adaptive Podcasting Player is responsible
            for the content. If you see any interactive podcast that you believe infringes another
            party&apos;s copyright or is inappropriate or offensive or illegal then you can report
            it to the creator.</p>
            <p>You may access and play interactive podcasts created by Adaptive Podcasting Editor on
            Adaptive Podcasting Player, as long as your use is lawful and you comply with these
            terms of use:</p>
            <p>You can only use Adaptive Podcasting Player to listen to an interactive story created
            by Adaptive Podcasting Editor.</p>
            <p>You cannot modify Adaptive Podcasting Player or decompile or reverse engineer it.</p>
            <p>You can only use the Adaptive Podcasting Player for non-commercial personal use on
            your personal device.</p>
            <p>Don&apos;t copy, distribute or license Adaptive Podcasting Player to anyone else.</p>
            <p>You must immediately stop using Adaptive Podcasting Player where the BBC asks to do
            so for any reason.</p>
            <p>If you install Adaptive Podcasting Player you also accept the BBC Terms of Use, which
            can be found at <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/terms">https://www.bbc.co.uk/terms</a>.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>